{
  "1": {
    "question": "Cell phones have become a permanent _ in modern society. Most people could not imagine living without one.",
    "answer": "fixture",
    "1": "clasp",
    "2": "stint",
    "3": "fixture",
    "4": "rupture"
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "Colin did not have enough money to pay for the car all at once, so he paid it off in _ of $800 a month for two years.",
    "answer" : "installments",
    "1": "dispositions",
    "2": "installments",
    "3": "enactments",
    "4": "speculations"
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "When she asked her boss for a raise, Melanie’s _ tone of voice made it obvious how nervous she was.",
    "answer" : "diffident",
    "1": "garish",
    "2": "jovial",
    "3": "pompous",
    "4": "diffident"
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "The religious sect established a _ in a rural area where its followers could live together and share everything. No private property was allowed.",
    "answer" : "commune",
    "1": "dirge",
    "2": "prelude",
    "3": "repository",
    "4": "commune"
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "The famous reporter was fired for _ another journalist’s work. His article was almost exactly the same as that of the other journalist.",
    "answer" : "plagiarizing",
    "1": "alleviating",
    "2": "plagiarizing",
    "3": "inoculating",
    "4": "beleaguering"
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "Now that the local steel factory has closed down, the streets of the once busy town are lined with _ businesses. Most owners have abandoned their stores.",
    "answer" : "defunct",
    "1": "rhetorical",
    "2": "volatile",
    "3": "defunct",
    "4": "aspiring"
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "The meeting was supposed to _ by noon, but it was still going at 1:30 p.m. By then, most of the people were very hungry.",
    "answer" : "wind up",
    "1": "wind up",
    "2": "shell out",
    "3": "wear in",
    "4": "spill over"
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "The new prime minister’s economic policy focuses on _ inflation. He has promised to get prices under control as quickly as possible.",
    "answer" : "reining in",
    "1": "sounding out",
    "2": "stitching up",
    "3": "reining in",
    "4": "locking away"
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "The detective spent several months _ the circumstances surrounding the murder before he was able to discover who had done it.",
    "answer" : "digging into",
    "1": "tilting at",
    "2": "swinging around",
    "3": "digging into",
    "4": "bracing for"
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "The meeting was supposed to _ by noon, but it was still going at 1:30 p.m. By then, most of the people were very hungry.",
    "answer" : "wind up",
    "1": "wind up",
    "2": "shell out",
    "3": "wear in",
    "4": "spill over"
  }
}
